Jeremiah Wadsworth papers
Connecticut Historical Society
- I. Correspondence, 1768-1804
  - 1. Jeremiah Wadsworth Correspondence, February 1768-June 1774
    - General Correspondence, June-August 1792 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, September-December 1792 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 1793 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 1794 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, January-June 1795 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, July-August 1795 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, September-November 1795 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, December 1795 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, January 1796 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, February 1796 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, March-April 1796 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, May-December 1796 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1797-1798 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, January-July 1799 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, August-December 1799 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, January-March 1800 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, April-June 1800 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, July-December 1800 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, January-March 1801 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, April-December 1801 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, January-June 1802 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, July-December 1802 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 1803-1804 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, undated – alphabetical by author, A-G (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, undated – alphabetical by author, H-W (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, undated – mostly written by Jeremiah Wadsworth, some with no author given (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Account of Jean Suzanne, a major in the French Army who served with the American army, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Pamphlet on distillation, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Family correspondence, 1771-1776 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Family correspondence, January-October, 1778 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Family correspondence, February 1779-January 1780 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Family correspondence, April 1780-June 1781 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Family correspondence, July 1781-February 1782 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Family correspondence, March-November 1782 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Family correspondence, July 1783-March 1784 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Family correspondence, April 1784-July 1785 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Family correspondence, August 1785-January 1787 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Family correspondence, February 1787-January 1788 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Family correspondence, February-August 1788 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Family correspondence, September-December 1788 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Family correspondence, March-August 1789 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Family correspondence, April-July 1790 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Family correspondence, December 1790-April 1793 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Family correspondence, October 1798-July 1800 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Family correspondence, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - 2. Royal Flint, Peter Colt, John Jeffrey, and Barnabas Deane Correspondence, 1778-1801
    - Royal Flint correspondence, July-August 1778 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Royal Flint correspondence, September 1778 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Royal Flint correspondence, October 1778 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Royal Flint correspondence, November 1778 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Royal Flint correspondence, December 1778-January 1779 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Royal Flint correspondence, February-June 1779 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Royal Flint correspondence, August-November 1779 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Royal Flint correspondence, December 1779 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Royal Flint correspondence, January-February 1780 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, September-November 9, 1778 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, November 10, 1778-January 1779 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, April 1783-March 1784 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, April-July 1784 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, August-December 1784 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, January-July 1785 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, August-December 1785 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, February 1786-January 1787 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, February-March 1787 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, April-June 1787 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, July 1787-January 1788 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, February-May 1788 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, June-August 1788 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, September-December 1788 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, January-April 1789 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, May-June 1789 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, July-August 1789 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, September-November 1789 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Peter Colt correspondence, October-November 1792 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, September 1780-May 1781 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, August-September 1781 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, October-November 1781 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, December 1781 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, January-February 1782 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, March 1782 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, April 1782 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, May 1782 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, June 1782 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, July 1782 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, August 1782 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, September 1782 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, October 1782 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, November 1782 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, December 1782 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, January 1783 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, February-March 1783 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - John Jeffrey correspondence, April-October 1783 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Barnabas Deane correspondence, July 1781-January 1782 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Barnabas Deane correspondence, June 1782-January 1783 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Barnabas Deane correspondence, February 1783-March 1784 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Barnabas Deane correspondence, April, July 1787 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Barnabas Deane correspondence, May 1799, March 1801 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Barnabas Deane accounts, receipts and notes, 1786-1794 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - 3. Letter Books, 1778-1804
    - Letter book for the Commissary General, 1778 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Letter book, April 1778-August 1779 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Letter book, April 1778-May 1779 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Letter book, October-November 1778 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Letter book, November 1778- January 1779 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Letter book, January-March 1779 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Letter book, March-July 1779 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Letter book, July-September 1779 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Letter book, September-November 1779 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Letter book, November 1779-February 1780 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Letter book, December 1779-April 1780 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Letter book, April 1780-July 1781 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Letter book, June-September, 1780 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Letter book, October 1780-April 1781 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Letter book, November 1780-August 1781 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Letter book, April-August 1781 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Letter book, 1782-1793 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Letter book, March-June 1783 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Letter book, 1795-1804 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- II. Financial Documents, 1767-1848
  - 1. Jeremiah Wadsworth French Army Financial Documents, 1778-1797
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, 1778 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, July-November 1780 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, December 1780 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January-May 1781 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, June-October 1781 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, November-December 1781 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January-March 1782 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, April-June 1782 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, July-September 1782 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, October-November 1782 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, December 1782 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January-March 1783 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - French Army Receipts, invoices, and accounts, April-December 1783 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - French trip diary, September 1783-February 1784 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - French Army receipts, invoices and accounts, 1784-1783, 1797 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - French Army receipts, invoices and accounts, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - 2. Jeremiah Wadsworth Financial Documents, 1767-1815
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, 1767-1774 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January-August 1775 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, September-October 1775 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, November 1775 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, December 1775 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January 1776 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, February 1776 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, March-April 1776 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, May-August 1776 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, September 1776 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, October 1776 (1 of 3) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, October 1776 (2 of 3) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, October 1776 (3 of 3) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, November-December 1776 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January-March 1777 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, April-June 1777 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, July-September 1777 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, October-November 1777 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, December 1777 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January-March 1778 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, April-July 1778 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, August-December 1778 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January-April 1779 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, May-September 1779 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, October-December 1779 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January-April 1780 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, May-June 1780 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, July 1780 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, August-December 1780 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January-February 1781 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, March-April 1781 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, May-June 1781 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, July-August 1781 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, September-December 1781 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, January-October 1782 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, November-December 1782 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, 1783-1785 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, 1786-1798 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, 1799-1804 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Receipts, invoices, and accounts, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Accounts, 1766-1779 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Accounts, 1780 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Accounts, 1781-1784 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Accounts, 1785-1789 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Accounts, 1790-1802 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Accounts, 1803-1815, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Account book, 1767-1770 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Account book and journal, 1771-1775 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Journals, 1775 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Invoice book, 1775-1776 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Account book, 1775-1778 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Account book, November-December 1776 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Account book, Sawpitts, 1776 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Account books, 1776-1777 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Cash book, 1776-1777 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Waste book, 1776-1777 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Cash book, 1776-1779 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Cash book, 1777-1778 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Waste book, 1777-1778 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Provisions account book, 1777-1778 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Provisions account book, 1777-1779 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Continental waste book, May 1778-March 1779 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Cash book, 1778-1779 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Waste book, 1778-1779 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Account book for Commissary General, 1778-1780 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Account book for Commissary General, 1778-1780 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Waste books, 1780-1781 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Account books for receipts and invoices, 1780-1782 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Navy account book, 1780 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Cash book, 1781 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Account book for flour shipped to Newport, 1781 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Waste book, 1781-1782 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Receipt book, 1781-1783 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Waste books, 1782 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Memorandum of certificates, 1782 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Artillery waste book, 1782 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Blotter, 1783-1784 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Waste book, 1783-1784 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Joseph Ketchum receipts, 1779, 1781 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Joseph Ketchum receipts, 1781 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Joseph Ketchum receipts, 1782-1784 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Joseph Ketchum receipts, 1785-1789, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 3. Daniel Wadsworth Financial Papers, 1804
    - Account book for settlement of Jeremiah Wadsworth’s estate, 1804 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Inventory and records of Mehitable and Jeremiah Wadsworth’s estates, 1804-1823 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Daniel Wadsworth Rondineau estate papers, 1792-1814 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Daniel Wadsworth Rondineau estate papers, 1813-1814 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Daniel Wadsworth and Paulina Marsen financial documents and correspondence, 1812-1842 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Daniel Wadsworth and Nathaniel Terry financial documents and correspondence, 1817-1839 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Daniel Wadsworth and Nathaniel Terry financial documents and correspondence, 1817-1841 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Daniel Wadsworth receipts and notes, 1828-1837 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Daniel Wadsworth correspondence with Terry family, 1825-1847 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Daniel Wadsworth account book, 1830-1847 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Daniel Wadsworth financial documents and correspondence with Edward P. Terry, 1831-1842 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Daniel Wadsworth financial documents and correspondence with Terry family, 1831-1847 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Daniel Wadsworth accounts and correspondence with Terry family, 1835, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Daniel Wadsworth and Nathaniel Terry correspondence, 1836-1841 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Daniel Wadsworth and Terry Family correspondence, 1836-1847 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Daniel Wadsworth correspondence with Terry family and lists of silver, 1847-1848, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
- III. Legal Documents, 1759-1848
  - Hartford deeds, alphabetically by surname of person granting deed, A-B, 1782-1803 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Hartford deeds, alphabetically by surname of person granting deed, C-D, 1782-1802 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Hartford deeds, alphabetically by surname of person granting deed, E-H, 1777-1800 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Hartford deeds, alphabetically by surname of person granting deed, J-L, 1781-1802 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Hartford deeds, alphabetically by surname of person granting deed, M-S, 1777-1801 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Hartford deeds, alphabetically by surname of person granting deed, T-Z, 1763-1803 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Hartford deeds, Daniel Wadsworth, 1791-1836 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Copy of will of John Winthrop from 1726, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Certificate of indenture for Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1759 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Agreement of creditors of Bernond Chauther, 1769 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Certificates of insurance, 1770-1774; 1787-1789 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Certificate appointing Matthew Talcott a Lieutenant Colonel in Connecticut’s sixth regiment, March 1775; certificate appointing Talcott a Colonel in Connecticut’s Twenty third regiment (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Government contract, 1776; Act of the General Assembly for the Continental Army, 1777 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Certificate of emancipation, 1777; bill of sale for slave Mark 1778 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Dartmouth college certificate, 1792; charter from the state of Vermont 1791; French documents, 1792 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence and papers concerning treaty with Indians (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Proposal to build a market in Hartford, 1796; Horse breeder’s certificate, 1796; receipt for purchase of land, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Agreement regarding an election day ball, 1797; Act of Congress for land in western reserve of Connecticut, 1798; bill regarding judicial courts in the United States, 1800 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Letter regarding Wadsworth’s estate, undated; Yale college document, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Articles of agreement for partnership between Nathaniel Greene, Jeremiah Wadsworth, and Barnabas Deane, 1779; copy of document granting Greene land in North Carolina, 1785; Greene estate Letter book (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Act authorizing creation of a road in Tennessee’s Davidson and Sumner counties (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Map of Greene property in Albany, New York (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Jeremiah Wadsworth correspondence regarding Genesee Land and Phelps-Gorham Purchase (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Jeremiah and Daniel Wadsworth correspondence regarding Genesee Land and Phelps-Gorham Purchase (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Jeremiah Wadsworth and George Dinnis maps, deeds, and memos for Genesee land (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Survey for the creation of a map of Connecticut, January 1789 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Genesee land records and maps, 1789-1802 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Jeremiah Wadsworth Genesee land deeds (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Jeremiah Wadsworth deeds and contracts for Genesee land and Phelps-Gorham purchase (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Jeremiah Wadsworth, James Wadsworth, George Dinnis, and William Judd Genesee land deeds (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Timothy Seymour deeds for Enosburgh, Vermont (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Sales of land (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Deeds and receipts for Vermont land on west side of mountains (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Jeremiah and Daniel Wadsworth deeds and contracts for Vermont land on west side of mountains (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Jeremiah and Daniel Wadsworth deeds and receipts for Vermont land on west side of mountains (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Jeremiah and Daniel Wadsworth correspondence and receipts for land in Richford, Vermont (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Jeremiah and Daniel Wadsworth correspondence and notes for land in Richford, Vermont (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Daniel Wadsworth deeds and correspondence for Vermont lands (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Jeremiah and Daniel Wadsworth deeds and receipts for Vermont land on west side of mountains (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - James and Jeremiah Wadsworth letter book for Genesee lands (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Jeremiah and Daniel Wadsworth correspondence regarding Phelps-Gorham purchase and Genesee land (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Jeremiah and Daniel Wadsworth correspondence and deeds for Vermont land (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Daniel Wadsworth deeds and maps for Talcott Mountain (Farmington) (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Daniel Wadsworth land records (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Daniel Wadsworth correspondence regarding land in Utica (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wyllys Hall papers: mortgages, correspondence with Daniel Wadsworth (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Richard Post papers: deeds, mortgages, certificates, financial papers (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Daniel Wadsworth correspondence regarding Genesee Land and Phelps-Gorham Purchase (Box 39, Folder 6)
- IV. Wadsworth and Carter papers, 1780-1787
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, October-November 1780 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, December 1780-March 1781 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, April-June 1781 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, July 1781-February 1782 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, March-April 1782 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, May-July 1782 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, September 1782 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, October 1782 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, November-December 1782 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, February-June 1783 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, July-December 18, 1783 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Wadsworth and Church, December 24, 1783-March 1784 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, April-June 1784 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Wadsworth and Church correspondence, July 1784-July 1785 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Wadsworth and Church correspondence, August 1785-January 1787 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Wadsworth and Carter correspondence, July 1787 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Wadsworth and Carter letter book, 1782-1785 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Wadsworth and Carter French Army account book, 1780 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Wadsworth and Carter French Army accounts, April-September 1781 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Wadsworth and Carter French Army accounts, December 1781-March 1782 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Wadsworth and Carter French Army accounts, April-June 1782 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Wadsworth and Carter French Army accounts, July-September 1782 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth and Carter French Army accounts, October 1782 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth and Carter French Army accounts, November 1782 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Wadsworth and Carter French Army accounts, December 1782 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Wadsworth and Carter French Army accounts, 1783 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Wadsworth and Carter French Army accounts, 1784, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, January-September 1780 (Box 41, Folder 8)